organizedhome.com 2003-12-04

# Privacy Policy - OrganizedHome.Com

###### organizedhome.com:  privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

##### Your Privacy is Important to Us

In an effort to support privacy policy disclosures on the Internet, Threadneedle Press wishes to set an example for other Web sites by voluntarily making our privacy policy available to the public. We urge all other Web sites to do the same. 

##### Privacy Policy Statement

This information pertains to the following sites, all of which are wholly owned by Threadneedle Press: 

  * OrganizedHome.Com

For each visitor to our Web pages, our Web server automatically recognizes the name of the domain through which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you use America Online); the date and time you access our site; the Internet address from which you linked to our site (the Web page you "clicked" from to get to our page); and the individual address of the computer you used to access our site. We use this information to administer our Web site, to help diagnose and troubleshoot potential server malfunctions, and to gather broad demographic information. 

We collect aggregate information on what pages users access or visit and information volunteered by the user, such as specific requests by users to be added to our newsletter mailing list. 

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. It is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify users about updates to our Web sites or for the receipt of our newsletters (but only if specifically requested to do so by the user) and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

##### Cookies

Threadneedle Press uses browser cookies to facilitate your experience with our products and services.  These cookies are small sections of code that our server sends to your browser which it can then store on your hard drive.  If you choose to accept these cookies, they enable us to recognize that your browser has previously visited and used our site, products or services and, based on your browser's previous visits, assist us with tailoring the information and content, banners and promotions you view. 

An example of the customization allowed by the use of such cookies is to retain your preferred settings and last time visited for the message boards on our sites so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit.  These cookies do not collect, store or maintain your private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit or use the site or our products and services, and you can choose to refuse our cookie, delete our cookie from your hard drive or turn off the cookie at any time by updating your user profile preferences.

##### Third Party Advertising

We use DoubleClick's Network, Sonar, and other third-party  advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use information (not including your name,  address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.sonar.com/naiprivacy>

##### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party   
advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your   
browser.

You can immediately opt-out of Doubleclick's unique cookies and   
have it switched to a non-unique cookie by clicking here   
<http://www.doubleclick.net/cgi-bin3/optout/check2.pl>

You will have to repeat this process if your cookies get deleted or   
you move to a new computer. More information on opting out of   
Doubleclick's cookies can be found at <http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm>

##### **Newsletter Subscription**

Threadneedle Press sites offer an option to subscribe to periodic newsletters regarding site updates, articles and news items. The only piece of information required is the user's e-mail address, which is only used to distribute the requested newsletter. 

##### Postings on Message Boards

It is important for you to remain aware that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on any message board, that information is available to any other person or user having access and use of that message board, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage you from offering any personally identifying information within a posting to any message board.

##### Contact for Privacy Inquiries:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or other questions about privacy on the Threadneedle Press sites, please contact:

Via Mail: 

|  | 

Threadneedle Press   
  
---|---|---  
|   | 

Privacy Administrator   
  
|   | 

PO Box 6791   
  
|   | 

Kennewick, WA   99352   
  
|  |   
  
Via E-Mail: 

|   |
